(Professor Proton(on youtube):)-Oh, shut up.
(Amy:)Watching your
old friend?
(Sheldon:)Yes. Look at him, Amy.
(Sheldon:)It's such a shame.
(Sheldon:)Struck down
in the prime of my life.
(Amy:)Do you want me to go to
the funeral with you?
(Sheldon:)-I'm not going to the funeral.
-Why not?
(Sheldon:)All those people
blowing their noses.
(Sheldon:)You can't tell the sick
from the sad.
(Sheldon:)I'll be at home celebrating
Star Wars Day, as planned.
(Amy:)Are you sure you don't
want to go say good-bye?
(Sheldon:)Amy, mourning the inevitable
is a complete waste of time.
(Amy:)And watching a bunch
of goofy space movies
(Amy:)you've seen hundreds
of times isn't?
(Sheldon:)If we were in
a physical relationship,
(Sheldon:)you just lost sex tonight.
(Penny:)Hey, guys.
(Raj:)Hey, Penny.
Happy Star Wars Day.
(Howard:)OK.